Minnesota.
Two picks in a row from the Vikings.
With the 97th pick in the 2026 NFL
Draft, the Minnesota Vikings select
Caleb Tiernan, tackle, Northwestern.
Yeah, he was the next tackle on my list,
so thought this about the range he would
come off the board. He's real patient in
pass protection. I think you're you like
what you see from him there with his
footwork. The anchor is just a little
bit late. He'll get moved a little bit
before settling down, but someone who I
think has the opportunity to be a
starting tackle. He's almost 6'8", 323
lbs. Doesn't have the longest arms,
plays a little bit high, but he's got
quick feet. He's patient in pass
protection, and he can slide mirror all
day long. He started 38 games at
Northwestern. They told me he's part of
that 5:00 a.m. club. You know how that's
a fad now, this 5:00 a.m. club. He was
in the building at 5:00 a.m. most days.